You're aiming for a flower swamp, right?
花の沢とか目指してるでしょ?
No, I am.
いや、してる
Laugh, laugh, totally.
笑 笑 全 然
Isn't Tarakamine a little similar?
タラカミネもちょっと似てない?
It is said.
言われます
Will you tell me?
言われるの?
LOL Hana no Sawa...
笑 花の沢...
They look alike, really.
似てるもん、本当に
is that so.
そうですか
lol Can I say that?
笑 言っていい?
lol The color is very white.
笑 色めっちゃ白いね
Is it white?
白いんですか?
As expected...
さすが...
As expected from Kanazawa people.
さすが金沢の人だよ
lol White.
笑 白い
Are there a lot of white people in Hanazawa?
花沢の人って、みんなこんなに白い人が多いんですか?
I think it's white.
白いと思います
Hey.
ねえ
not at all.
全然
not at all?
全然?
I want to be nervous.
緊張したくて
I was nervous.
緊張しました
If you find out, you're out, already.
バレたらアウトだからね、もう
It's a quick production.
速攻作処だよ
Yeah.
うん
I'm already ashamed.
もう、恥じてる
I think it's too late to delete it from Balti any time soon.
いつのままバルティから削除しても遅いと思うけどね
slow.
遅い
Is that something?
なんか、あれですか?
Did you play sports?
スポーツしてました?
I was playing sports.
スポーツしてました
what have you been up to?
何してたの?
tennis.
テニス
It wasn't tennis, so it was quite...
テニスじゃなかったから、なかなかこの...
Is it beautiful?
綺 麗 なのか
I.
私が
In the future, you're already aiming for a flower swamp, right?
将来はね、もう花の沢とか目指してるでしょ?
I knew.
知ってた
Don't you know?
知ってないの?
not at all.
全然
Isn't Tarakamine a little similar?
タラカミネもちょっと似てない?
It is said.
言われます
Are you told?
言われる?
They look alike, really.
似てるもん、本当に
I did it.
やった
It's cute.
可愛いもんね
You're wearing cute clothes.
可愛い服着てるね
This is how I came, uncle.
こうやって来ましたよ、おじさん
Should I remove this button?
このボタンまで外しちゃおうかな
I'm used to the time.
時間慣れしてるから
It's delicious.
うまいね
Unbutton this area.
この辺までボタン外せろ
Those are nice pants.
よろしいパンツだね、それ
Please take a look at this.
ちょっと見てください、これ
It turned out like this.
こんなになっちゃいました
Like this?
こんな?
Have you seen it?
見たことある?
It's beautiful.
綺麗なんだよ
Spread it yourself and see.
自分でマンク広げてほら
Can I have my uncle's nipples licked?
おじさんの乳首に舐めてもらっていい?
It's big.
大きいね
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Can I open it again?
もう一度開けていい?
Looks like I'm going.
行きそう
Can I go?
行っていい?
go.
行く
It seemed like I had pushed it in too far and it came out.
奥に入れすぎてたみたいで出てきたから
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Looks like I pushed it too far in.
奥に入れすぎてたみたいでさ
Can I ask you to tell me your impressions of the first shoot?
初撮りの感想を一言お願いしていい?
It was embarrassing.
恥ずかしかったです
Which side?
どの辺が?
I wonder what I should do.
どうやったらいいんやろうと
That's right.
ですよね
It was very well done.
すごくうまくできてたよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
That’s it, right?
あれでしょ?
Are you aiming for flowers or something?
花草とか目指してるでしょ?
I'm doing it.
してる
Haven't you?
してないの?
not at all.
全然
Doesn't she look a little like Minami Tanaka?
田中みなみにちょっと似てない?
It is said.
言われます
Will it be said?
言 われる?
They really look alike.
似てるもん本当に
Can I go?
行っていい?